Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
- Box: 30, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Los Sindicatos y la Amenaza Totalitaria, 1955; Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Author: Ricardo Temoche Benites
  - Item 7: Program of the Department for Economic and Social Research, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Que es la ORIT?, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Que es la ORIT?, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Report on the Meeting of the Economic Commission for Latin-America, 1951; Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Statement on Economic and Social Development Program for Latin-America, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Interpretandonos, 1957; Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Author: Luis Alberto Monge
  - Item 13: The Permanent Struggle of the Free Trafe Union Movement Against Latin American Dictatorships, 1960; Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Author: Inter-American Regional Organization of Workers of ICFTU
- Box: 30, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Agricultural Labor in the Americas, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: La Situation Laboral en la Cuba Castrista, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Manual del Organizador, 1963; Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Author: Guillermo Lora
  - Item 4: The Cuban Trade Union Movement under the regime of Dr. Castro, 1960; Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Author: Inter-American Regional Organization of Wrokers of the ICFTU
  - Item 5: United States Section, Joint United States-Mexico Trade Union Committee, 1958; Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Vocabulario Sindical: Trade Union Vocabulary, 1961; Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Author: ORIT (Organization). Dept. of Education
  - Item 7: III Continental Congress, Secretary General's Report, 1955; Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, News Clippings, 1953; Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Notes: news clippings
  - Item 9: Study on Inflation, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: El Movimiento Sindical de Venezuela victima del despotismo militar, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Box: 30, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Convocatoria a la Conferencia Sindical de los Trabajadores de America Latina, 1962; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Facts and Figures, 1953; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol II., No. 4, September- October 1953
  - Item 3: Facts and Figures, 1958; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol VII, No 3-4, March-April 1958
  - Item 4: Facts and Figures, 1952; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 6/7, July-August 1952
  - Item 5: Facts and Figures, 1952; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 8/9, October- November 1952
  - Item 6: Facts and Figures, 1952; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. 1, Nr. 10, December 1952
  - Item 7: Facts and Figures, 1952; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. 1, Nr. 5, June 1952
  - Item 8: Facts and Figures, 1951; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. I, No. 1, January 1951
  - Item 9: Facts and Figures, 1953; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. II, No. 3, June-August 1953
  - Item 10: Facts and Figures, 1953; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. II., No. 1, February- March 1953
  - Item 11: Facts and Figures, 1952; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. L, No. 8, September 1952
  - Item 12: Los Sindicatos, Lo Que Son, Lo Que Hacen Su Estructura, 1962; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Opinions and Recommendations Presented by the CTM to the VI ORIt-ICFTU Continental Congress, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: The Role of the Free Trade Union Movement in the Caribbean and the West Indies During their New Phases of Political, Economic and Social Development. Their Total Integration into the Inter-American Community, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Box: 30, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Comision de Credenciales, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Como Llegar a las Bases Sindicales, Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Datos y Cifras, 1961; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Departamento de Educacion, Silabo, 1963; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Honorable Members of the Executive Body of the Congress, Honored Guests, Fellow Delegates, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Instituto Americano Para el Desarrolla del Sindicalismo Libre: Terminologia Laboral de Uso Mas Corriente en Los Estados Unidos, Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Instituto Interamericano de Altos Estudios Sindicales Informe del Segundo Curso Realizado entre el 10 de Agosto y el 8 de Octubre de 1962, Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Introduction to the Report of the Secretariat on ORIT Activities between the V and VI Congresses, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Manual de Prensa Obrera, 1957; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Manuel del Organizador, 1963; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Opinions and Recommendations Presented by the CTM to the VI ORIT-ICFTU Continental Congress, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: The Permanent Struggle of the Free Trade Union Movement Against Latin American Dictatorships, 1960; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: Address Delivered by the President of the ICFTU, Mr. Arne Geijer, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Address Delivered by the Secretary General of the ICFTU Omer Becu at the Opening Ceremonies of the VI ORIT Continental Congress, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Address Delivered by the Secretary General of the ORIT at the Opening Ceremones of the VI ORIT Continental Congress, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 16: Address Delivered by the Secretary General of the ORIT at the Opening Ceremonies of the VI ORIT Continental Congress, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: Address Delivered by the Secretary General of the ORIT at the Opening Ceremonies of the VI ORIT Continental Congress, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: Address Delivered by the Secretary General of the ORIT at the Opening Ceremonies of the VI ORIT Continental Congress, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Resolution No. 4 Presented by the Confederation of Workers of Peru (CTP) with Relation to the Reduction of the Export Sugar Quota, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: Resolution No.1 Presented by the Peruvian Delegation to the VI ORIT Continental Congress, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 21: Draft Resolution No. 2 Presented by the Peruvian Delegation to the VI ORIT Continental Congress, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 22: Tabla No. 1, Chart No. 1, Numero de Participantes en Cada Curso, por Paises, 1964; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 23: Address delivered by Julio Santos Coy, Under-Secretary of the Ministry of Labor and Social Welfare, at the Opening Ceremonies of the VI ORIT Continental Congress, 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 24: Remarks by Francisco Perez Leiros (Argentina), 1965; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 25: El Movimiento Sindical Cubano bajo el regimen del Dr. Castro, 1960; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 26: Report on the First Inter-American Trade Union Economic Conference, 1961; Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
    Author: ORIT (Organization). Dept. of Economic and Social Affairs
- Box: 30, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Antecedentes Historicos de la Vida Sindical, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Box: 30, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Constitution 1955, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Constitution 1957, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Constitution as revised by the Sixth World Congress, 1959; Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Constitution of the International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1950; Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Constitution of the International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1951; Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Constitution of the International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1951; Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Box: 30, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: On the Tenth Anniversary of ORIT and Before its 5th Continental Congress, 1961; Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Press Release No. 4-58, U.S.-Mexico Trade Union Group Calls on Secretary of Labor to Renew Plea to Congress for Funds to Protect Braceros, 1958; Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Report of the First Inter-American Conference of Directors of Labor Education Held by ORIT, 1964; Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Report on the 5th Continental Congress of the Inter-American Regional Organization of Workers, 1961; Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Report on the First Inter-American Trade Union Economic Conference, 1961; Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Statement of the United States Section, Joint United States-Mexico Trade Union Committee Presented by Paul K. Reed, Treasurer before the House Agriculture Subcommittee, 1958; Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: The Philosophic Principles which Determine the Action of the Free International Trade Union Movement, 196; Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Trade Unions and People of Cuba Against Despotism, 1961; Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Vocabulario Sindical Trade Union Vocabulary de la ORIT, 1960; Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Vocabulario Sindical Trade Union Vocabulary ORIT, 1962; Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: III Continental Congress, 1955; Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Box: 31, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report on the International Federation of Christian Trade Unions and the Trade Union National Centers Affiliated to it, 1946; Publication (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Box: 31, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Document: World Labor Manifesto, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions Congress 1949: Economic and Social Demands: Manifesto, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions Congress 1949: Economic and Social Demands: Manifesto, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions: Its Organization, Objectives, Ideology and Structure, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Some Facts about the ICFTU -- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: New World Labor Organization Established, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Author: Anthony P. Alfino
  - Item 7: Prepatory International Trade Union Conference, Geneva, Switzerland - June 25-26, 1949, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: For Bread, Peace and Freedom: Decisions of the First World Congress of the ICFTU, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Author: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. World Congress
  - Item 9: For Bread, Peace and Freedom: Decisions of the First World Congress of the ICFTU, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Box: 31, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Datos complementarios al informe sobreinversiones sindicales, Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Desarrolla Sindical, 1964; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Funcion Social del Credito, 1964; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Instrucciones a los Vocales del Congreso, Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Mr. M.F. Neufeld, Observador Extranjero Estados Unidos, 1964; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Constitution of the International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Description and Analysis of Job Evaluation Systems, 1947; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Author: Edward Joseph
  - Item 8: ICFTU Regional Organizations, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Author: David Saposs
  - Item 9: Memorandum on the trade union and labour situation, Federation of Malaya, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Author: John A. Brazier
    Notes: several small reports bound together
  - Item 10: New World Labor Organization Established, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Restricted: ICFTU Emergency Committee Meeting, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Restricted: Report on the ICFTU Emergency Committee Meeting, Brussels, March 15-18, 1950, Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Author: D. Saposs
  - Item 13: Under-Developed Areas, ICFTU Program and Activities, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Author: Nelson H. Cruikshank
  - Item 14: World Labor Manifesto, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: World Labor's New Weapon, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Author: David Dubinsky
- Box: 31, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Organization structure of syndical movement - (drawing), 1964; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: How Labor Fights the Cold War, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Author: Irving Brown
  - Item 3: ICFTU Second World Congress, Milan, Italy, July 4-12, 1951, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Labor Participation in International affairs, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Problems Attendant on Formation of Non-Communist Trade Union International, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Resolution No. 13, Voluntary Contributions to Support the Regional Activities of the ICFTU, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Resolutions adopted by the World Congress of Professional Employees sponsored by the International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Workers of Africa!, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Workers of the World - United, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Author: J.H. Oldenbroek
  - Item 10: Stalin's Slave Camps, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Author: Charles A. Orr
- Box: 31, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: General Report on the Three Fortnightly Trade Union Training Courses organized at the Hjalmar Branting Institute, Chateau de la Breviere (St. Jean aux Bois, Oise), 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: General Report on the Three Fortnightly Trade Union Training Courses organized at the Hjalmar Branting Institute, Chateau de la Breviere (St. Joan aux Bois, Oise), 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Handbook on Workers Education in the World - correspondence, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Peron Unmasked: The Martyrdom of the Free Trade Union Movement in Argentina, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Trade Union Education in a Changing World, Tasks for trade union education in Asia, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Author: V.S. Mathur
- Box: 31, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: ICFTU Study Guide 2: Problems of International Migration, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Draft Report of the International Seminar on Workers' Education, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions: Some Facts about the ICFTU - its aims, its programme, its structure, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The Resolutions of the International Trade Section Conferences -- International Federation of Commercial, Clerical and Technical Employees Newsletter, No. 9, November 1953, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Author: International Federation of Commercial, Clerical, and Technical Employees
  - Item 5: Message to the Governmental Delegations to the Eighth United Nations General Assembly on the Racial Problem in South Africa, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Statement on Full Employment, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Structure, Functions and Problems of the ICFTU, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: ICFTU Study Guide 1: Economic Systems in Change, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: ICFTU: Free Trade Unions of the Whole World March Together towards a Better Life for All, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Workers fists against Soviet Steel, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Workers' Fists against Soviet Steel, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: ICFTU: Free Trade Unions of the Whole World March Together towards a Better Life for All, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: ICFTU: Free Trade Unions of the Whole World March Together towards a Better Life for All, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Workers' Fists against Soviet Steel, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Box: 31, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Another Hoax! An Exposure of the WFTU Charter of Trade Union Rights, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Another Hoax! An Exposure of the WFTU Charter of Trade Union Rights, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Another Hoax! An Exposure of the WFTU Charter of Trade Union Rights, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Another Hoax! An Exposure of the WFTU Charter of Trade Unions Rights, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: European Regional Organisation of the ICFTU: Fifth Meeting of the European Advisory Committee on Education, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Free Labor Means a Free World: The New York Times, Labor Unity Abroad, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: International Trade Unions Training Centre: Summary of a provisional Programme of Studies, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Report of the Fourth World Congress, ICFTU, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Author: Donald McDonald
  - Item 9: Trade Unions - What they are, What they do, Their structure -- Trade Union Study Notes 1, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: How to Collect Union Dues -- Your Union Problems Series No. 1, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Los sindicatos: lo que son, lo que hacen, su estructura -- Cover title: Notas de Estudios Sindicales, 1955; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Author: ORIT (Organization). Departamento de Educacion
- Box: 31, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Foreign Affairs anf the AFL-CIO, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions Message on Assistance to Economically Underdeveloped Countries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: The Vienna ICFTU Congress, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: The Vienna ICFTU Congress, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Training the World's Trade Unionists, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Training the World's Trade Unionists, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Training the World's Trade Unionists, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: The Organisation of the Workers of the World -- ICFTU, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: The Spanish People Strike Back at Franco, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Women! It's your fight too!, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: The ICFTU and the Workers of Morocco, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Box: 31, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report on Hungary: The ICFTU Summary of the UN Special Committee's Report on the Problem of Hungary, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Author: United Nations. General Assembly. Special Committee on the Problem of Hungary
  - Item 2: Communist Onslaught Aims to Crack Free Trade Unions, Duel for Asian-African Workers Nears Climax, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Message on the Work of the High Commissioner for Refugees -- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Translation of Letter from International Confederation of Free Trade Unions to the United Nations High Comissioner for Refugees, 1957; Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: The Organisation of the Workers of the World -- ICFTU, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Education: The Key to Labour Progress - A survey of trade union education past, present, and future, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Author: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. International Seminar, Oberursel, Germany, and Brussels, 1958.
- Box: 31, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Free Trade Unions in the Developing Democracies, 1959; Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Author: C.H. Millard
    Notes: specially reprinted from International Journal
  - Item 2: ICFTU After Ten Years: Problems and Prospects, 1961; Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1959; Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: A College of Their Own, 1959; Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Notes: specially reprinted from Free Labour World
  - Item 5: ICFTU: The First Ten Years, 1959; Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: The Organisation of the Workers of the World -- ICFTU, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: In the Heart of Mother Africa, 1959; Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Collective Bargaining - Teaching Guide for Union Training No. II, 1959; Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Women Workers: You need the Trade Unions, the Trade Unions need You, 1958; Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Box: 31, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Formacion Sindical, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Formacion Sindical, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Formacion Sindical, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Box: 31, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Free Trade Unions in the Fight for African Freedom, 1961; Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: ICFTU After Ten Years: Problems and Prospects, 1961; Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: The History of Trade Unions in Latin America, 1959; Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: ICFTU Statement to the 17th General Assembly of the United Nations, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions Memorandum to the Seventeeth Session of the General Assembly of the United Nations On the Discrimination Against Jews in the USSR, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Report of the Joint IFBWW.IFPAAW/ICFTU Mission of Investigation into the John Thalmayer Case (Turkey, 9-12 September 1962), Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Leadership and Administration in the ICFTU: A New Phase of Development, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: The College on the Equator: The Story of the ICFTU Educational Activities in Africa, 1964; Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
    Author: Albert Hammerton
  - Item 9: Asian Trade Union College - The First Decade, 1962; Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
    Author: Mark Starr
  - Item 10: International Trade Secretariats -- Know Your Facts No. 8, 1962; Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
    Author: International Trade Secretariats
- Box: 31, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Leadership and Administration in the ICFTU: A New Phase of Development, Publication (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Administrative Problems of the International Labor Movement (Alternate Title: The ICFTU Under New Management), Publication (Box 31, Folder 13)